In ComfyUI, we open the free master
workflow and select our Laura in the
power loader. Write a simple prompt with
your trigger word and hit run. Look at
the result. I think it's okay, but it
can be done much better. The Laura is
doing exactly what we trained her for.
And to be fair, this image is already
good, but we can push the realism way
more. Here's the thing, on the RunPod
template, I already added a few Lauras
for you. Nothing to download, they're
also already on the pod. The two I use
the most is the Realistic Snapshot Laura
and the Nice Girls Ultra Realistic
Laura. Big credits to the creators, they
are both insane. For this one, we go
with the Realistic Snapshot because for
me it's the best realism Laura for the
image turbo right now. So, we set it up
with our character Laura and click
generate again. Look at the difference.
Same girl, but now it looks way better
in my opinion.